<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Root>
  <Node ID="0">
    starting point
    <Address>100</Address>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="100" Char="Alex">
    <Text>"November 27, 1920. I'm entering the once-renowned Countryshire Apartments, where actors and singers used to stay. But now, tragedy has struck this high-class residence with the death of..."</Text>
    <Address>101 201</Address>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="101" Char="Steve">
    <Text>I'm sorry, miss, but were you talking to me?</Text>
    <Address>102</Address>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="102" Char="Alex">
    <Text>No, I'm sorry. I was recording myself so that I can write it down later.</Text>
    <Address>103 105</Address>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="103" Char="Steve">
    <Text>I see. So what floor will it be?</Text>
    <Address>104</Address>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="104" Char="Alex">
    <Text>Oh, never mind! I'll just walk back to my room, I have to write this down ASAP!</Text>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="105" Char="Steve">
    <Text>I see, so you're a reporter. So you're researching the accident that happened here?</Text>
    <Reputation>+1</Reputation>
    <Address>600</Address>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="201" Char="Steve">
    <Text>It's kind of rude to ignore someone that's right in front of you. Anyway, which floor?</Text>
    <Reputation>-1</Reputation>
    <Address>202</Address>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="202" Char="Alex">
    <Text>Sorry, normally people just ignore me and go about their lives. I was talking to my tape recorder, I'm working on a new story.</Text>
    <Address>203 105</Address>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="203" Char="Steve">
    <Text>Well, if you say so. What floor, ma'am?</Text>
    <Address>204</Address>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="204" Char="Alex">
    <Text>Never mind, I'll just walk back to my room. I have to get this down before I forget it!</Text>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="600" Char="Alex">
    <Text>I'm here because of an incident that happened awhile ago. I came in part due to the apartments' upper-class reputation, but now I'm very interested in the death of Mr. Lindson.</Text>
    <Address>601</Address>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="601" Char="Alex">
    <Text>I have too many ideas I want to remember! I'll just walk back to my room. Thank you, sir!</Text>
  </Node>
</Root>