<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Root>
  <Node ID="0">
    starting point
    <Address>100</Address>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="100" Char="Caroline">
    <Text>Good evening. To the fourth floor, please.</Text>
    <Address>101 201</Address>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="101" Char="Steve" ShowOnce="True">
    <Text>It's rather late to be out and about.</Text>
    <Address>102 103</Address>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="102" Char="Caroline">
    <Text>One could say that. I had important business to attend to.</Text>
    <Address>201 600</Address>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="103" Char="Caroline">
    <Text>Yes, well... I suppose I've known you long enough now that it wouldn't hurt to tell you the truth...</Text>
    <Address>104</Address>
    <Threshold>7</Threshold>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="104" Char="Caroline">
    <Text>Every few days, I visit my son's grave. I buy flowers for him when I visit. I'd like to think he appreciates them, even though he's gone.</Text>
    <Address>105 201 600</Address>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="105" Char="Steve">
    <Text>I'm so sorry for your loss. What happened to him?</Text>
    <Address>106</Address>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="106" Char="Caroline">
    <Text>Years ago, Mr. Lindson owned a construction site near the coal mines in town. My husband used to work there.</Text>
    <Address>107</Address>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="107" Char="Caroline">
    <Text>After he passed, our son began to work there, too. I suppose he wanted to make his father proud, but I warned him not to go. I didn't want to lose him.</Text>
    <Address>108</Address>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="108" Char="Caroline">
    <Text>Just a few months after he started, there was some sort of demolitions accident at the construction site. It caused a collapse in the mines where my son was working that day.</Text>
    <Address>109</Address>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="109" Char="Caroline">
    <Text>...as you can guess, he didn't escape alive. Mr. Lindson never apologized to any of the victims. And now I've been here, alone, for many years.</Text>
    <Address>110 201 600</Address>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="110" Char="Steve">
    <Text>That's terrible. I didn't know...</Text>
    <Address>111</Address>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="111" Char="Caroline">
    <Text>And how could you have known? The whole thing was covered up by that conniving man. Money makes mistakes disappear.</Text>
    <Address>112</Address>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="112" Char="Caroline">
    <Text>For years, I wished vengeance on him. I wished for him to feel the void that I do every day. In the end, he got his justice anyway.</Text>
    <Address>201 600</Address>
    <Hint>It sounds like her son's death could be a possible motive for murder.</Hint>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="201" Char="Steve" ShowOnce="True">
    <Text>What do you think of Lucy?</Text>
    <Address>202</Address>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="202" Char="Caroline">
    <Text>She's a bit too energetic sometimes. I don't know where she gets it all from! When I was her age, I was ready to settle down and have a quiet life. Changing times, I guess.</Text>
    <Address>203 101 600</Address>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="203" Char="Steve">
    <Text>And what do you think of Thomas?</Text>
    <Address>204 205</Address>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="204" Char="Caroline">
    <Text>I'm still not interested in gossip, dear. No need to drag down the conversation.</Text>
    <Reputation>-1</Reputation>
    <Address>101 600</Address>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="205" Char="Caroline">
    <Text>He's a quiet man. I can tell he has a troubled past weighing on his mind.</Text>
    <Threshold>6</Threshold>
    <Address>101 600</Address>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="600" Char="Steve">
    <Text>Have a good night, Caroline. (end conversation)</Text>
    <Address>601 602</Address>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="601" Char="Caroline">
    <Text>Thank you.</Text>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="602" Char="Caroline">
    <Text>Thank you, and you too, Steve.</Text>
  </Node>
</Root>