<Root>
  <Node ID="0">
    starting point
    <Address>100</Address>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="100" Char="Steve" NPC1="James" NPC2="">
    <Text>Good evening, Mr. James.</Text>
    <Address>101 201</Address>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="101" Char="James">
    <Text>Evening. This can't be happening... two deaths, both within such a short time?</Text>
    <Address>102 104</Address>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="102" Char="Steve">
    <Text>Yep. This doesn't look good for some of you. After all, you always keep secrets and seem to have a way with codes.</Text>
    <Address>103</Address>
    <Reputation>-2</Reputation>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="103" Char="James">
    <Text>Oh, is that so? I'll keep that in mind. I'll be going now.</Text>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="104" Char="Steve">
    <Text>I assure you everything will turn out fine, especially now that the police are here. Plus, the cause of death was just a snake bite.</Text>
    <Address>105</Address>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="105" Char="James">
    <Text>I know that you're right, but it doesn't help too much. It's going to be awhile before I feel safe at night...</Text>
    <Address>106</Address>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="106" Char="James">
    <Text>Thank you, Mr. Devlin. Have a good evening.</Text>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="201" Char="James">
    <Threshold>3</Threshold>
    <Text>Evening. You seem familiar with some of the cops in the building. Do you have any clues as to what's going on here?</Text>
    <Address>202 206</Address>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="202" Char="Steve">
    <Text>(tell him what you know)</Text>
    <Address>203</Address>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="203" Char="Steve">
    <Reputation>+1</Reputation>
    <Text>I do know some people on the force. They haven't been saying much, but they've found that the same poison was the cause of death for both victims. Don't worry, this should all be over soon.</Text>
    <Address>204</Address>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="204" Char="James">
    <Text>I hope it will. Thank you, Mr. Devlin. Good night.</Text>
    <Address>205</Address>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="205" Char="Steve">
    <Text>And to you.</Text>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="206" Char="Steve">
    <Text>(tell him you don't know anything)</Text>
    <Address>207</Address>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="207" Char="Steve">
    <Reputation>-2</Reputation>
    <Text>I have no idea what you're talking about. I'm not that friendly with the police, but I do know that Charles's death is being closely investigated.</Text>
    <Address>208</Address>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="208" Char="James">
    <Text>Huh, funny, because I recall that you used to be a part of the force with them.</Text>
    <Address>209</Address>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="209" Char="Steve">
    <Text>How do you know that?</Text>
    <Address>210</Address>
  </Node>
  <Node ID="210" Char="James">
    <Text>Word gets around, Mr. Devlin. We aren't as naive as you may think. Good night.</Text>
  </Node>
</Root>
